Jared Scarr

Seattle, WA

425-737-4786 | jaredscarr@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jaredscarr | github.com/jaredscarr | jaredscarr.com

I am a full stack developer with a strong background in end-user customer experience. I am focused on writing customer-centric and results driven code that bring solutions to the market and a companies bottom line.

Technical Skills

Python, Django, REST, Unnittest, Pytest, AWS, Ansible, Pyramid, JavaScript, JQuery, GitHub, Foundation 6, HTML, CSS, JSON, Postgresql, AJAX, PostGis

Projects

Cocktail Cost API, October 2016 - github.com/jaredscarr/bartrack

- Developed a RESTful API with the Pyramid framework.
- Inventory and cost management.

Portfolio, May 2016 - jaredscarr.com

- Designed a single page application using the Foundation 6 framework.
- Deployed on Amazon Web Services with EC2, CloudFront and Route 53 DNS.

RideShare, May 2016 - github.com/RideQuest/rideshare-backend

- Utilized a PostGIS spatial database and Google Maps to connect users based on their proximity to each other.
- Built a RESTful API for front end consumption with Django.

Work Experience

Software Developer, GMB Fitness, Seattle, WA

Sep 2016 – current

- Developing a script in Python to transfer data from Wistia to Vimeo
- Interfacing with both video cloud storage API's

Manager / Lead Instructor, Foundation CrossFit, Seattle, WA

Sep 2012 - Nov 2016

- Led athletes to achieve their goals in a strong, positive team culture
- Developed an innovative program that increased maximum capacity of athletes by 50%
- Piloted and organized events for charity and promotions

Bartender, Seattle WA

May 2004 - Jan 2015

- Delivered gracious and attentive service to guests
- Mixed cocktails at award-winning establishments like Canon, Rumba and Serafina
- Contributed to the creation of products for menus and events

Education

Code Fellows, Seattle, WA

Nov 2015 - May 2016

• Python Advanced Development Certificate, May 2016